<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145950177</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-hills/blackford-stable-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-hills/blackford-stable-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Blackford Stable Wines</name><region>Adelaide Hills</region><address1>
            PO Box 162, Charleston, SA 5244</address1><address2>
            
            Adelaide Hills
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.blackfordstable.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 8389 5312
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Nicky Cowper
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 8389 5313
        </facsimilie><description>
            Two odysseys lie entwined in the history of Blackford Stable. The first was that of Charles Newman, who left his home in Blackford, Somerset, UK, in 1837, aged 16, to (successfully) seek fame and fortune in Australia, and whose great-great-granddaughter and family live in the Blackford homestead. The second odyssey was that of the Cowper family, whose 18-year-old daughter Nicky moved from the beauty of NZs southern Hawkes Bay region to begin studies in oenology at the University of Adelaides Waite Institute, convincing her parents, Stephen and Angela, to follow her and relocate permanently to Australia. A property they purchased is part of the original Blackford estate; the stone stables are the embryonic home of Blackford Stable Wines. They have progressively planted 28ha of chardonnay, sauvignon blanc, semillon, riesling, pinot gris, merlot and cabernet sauvignon since 1998, selling most of the grapes while Nicky completed her studies and then worked vintages in the Barossa Valley, Adelaide Hills, McLaren Vale, Vic, France, the US and South Africa.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>