<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146044506</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/zitta-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/zitta-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Zitta Wines</name><region>Barossa Valley</region><address1>
            3 Union Street, Dulwich, SA 5065 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Barossa Valley
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.zitta.com.au</website><telephone>
            0419 819 414
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Angelo De Fazio
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 8331 1147
        </facsimilie><description>
            Owner Angelo De Fazio says that all he knows about viticulture and winemaking came from his father (and generations before him). It is partly this influence that has shaped the label and brand name: Zitta is Italian for quiet and the seeming reflection of the letters of the name Zitta is in fact nothing of the kind; turn the bottle upside down, and you will see it is the word Quiet. The Zitta vineyard dates back to 1864, with a few vines remaining from that time, and a block planted with cuttings taken from those vines. Shiraz dominates the plantings (22ha), the balance made up of chardonnay, grenache and a few mourvedre vines; only a small amount of the production is retained for the Zitta label. The property has two branches of the Greenock Creek running through it, and the soils reflect the ancient geological history of the site, in part with a subsoil of river pebbles reflecting the course of a long-gone river. Tradition there may be, but there is also some highly sophisticated writing and marketing in the background material and their website. Exports to China.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>