<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145993970</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/margaret-river/marq-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/margaret-river/marq-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Marq Wines</name><region>Margaret River</region><address1>
            2 Gibson Drive, Dunsborough, WA 6281 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Margaret River
            
            
        </address2><website>www.marqwines.com.au</website><telephone>
            0411 122 662
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Mark Warren
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Mark Warren has a degree in wine science from CSU and a science degree from the University of WA; to complete the circle, he is currently lecturing in wine science and wine sensory processes at Curtin University, Margaret River  the last position held for the past eight years. He also has 22 years experience in both the Swan Valley and Margaret River, and his current major commercial role is producing the extensive Happs range as well as wines under contract for several other Margaret River wine brands. When all of this is added up, he is responsible for 60 to 70 individual wines each year, now including six wines under his own Marq Wines label. A quick look at the list (Vermentino, Fiano,Wild Ferment Chardonnay, Gamay,Tempranillo and Malbec, with an Amarone Shiraz in the pipeline) points to the underlying philosophy: an exploration of the potential of alternative varieties and unusual winemaking methods by someone with an undoubted technical understanding of the processes involved. The wines are produced in very small amounts: 100200 dozen of each.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>