<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145986699</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/coonawarra/kopparossa-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/coonawarra/kopparossa-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Kopparossa Wines</name><region>Coonawarra</region><address1>
            Stentiford Vineyard, Lot 95 Skinner Road, Coonawarra, SA 5263</address1><address2>
            
            Coonawarra
            SA
            5263
        </address2><website/><telephone>
            (08) 8736 3268
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Gavin Hogg
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            24 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 8736 3363
        </facsimilie><description>
            Of the many complicated stories, this is one of the most complicated of all. Founded by Gavin Hogg and Mike Press in 1996 and based on an 80ha vineyard in the Wrattonbully region, the Kopparossa label was born in 2000. The vineyard was sold in 02, and Mike retired to pursue separate interests in his Adelaide Hills family vineyard. Various wine releases and events occurred until 05, when a joint venture between Stentiford Pty Ltd (Kopparossas parent company) and Estate Licensing Pty Ltd (Olivia Newton-Johns wine-naming rights company) was entered into. Says Gavins newsletter, Put simply, Stentiford produces and packages wine for the Olivia Label, which is then marketed and sold by Estate Licensing. Another complication followed in 09, when Gavin purchased a 24ha vineyard on the Murray River at Yelta, adjacent to his parents vineyard; as from vintage 11 the majority of the fruit from the 24ha Hoggies Vineyard is being used for Hoggies Estate brand, and for various private labels. Exports to the UK, the US, Canada, Vietnam, Hong Kong and China.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>