<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146030222</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/the-old-orchard-winery]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/the-old-orchard-winery]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>The Old Orchard Winery</name><region>Yarra Valley</region><address1>
            254 Scoresby Road, Boronia, Vic 3155</address1><address2>
            
            Yarra Valley
            VIC
            
        </address2><website>www.theoldorchardwinery.com.au</website><telephone>
            (03) 9801 2183
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Tony Pelosi, Jeff Wright
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            The establishment date of 1981 is the year during which 2.45ha of chardonnay, cabernet sauvignon, shiraz, cabernet franc and malbec were planted under a work for the dole scheme sponsored by Knox City Council on 8ha of Crown land in Boronia. Care of the vineyard changed hands several times until 2005 when the Council requested expressions of interest in operating the vineyard. English-born couple Pat and David Smith (who had married in Germany) had moved to Australia in 82, and settled down to separate business lives, David starting a software development business in 83, Pat becoming a long-term member of the Myer company until retiring in 04. During his time in Germany, David was responsible for buying French and German wines for a British retail chain that serviced British members of NATO, and part of his computer business was the installation of Dan Murphys first electronic point of sale system in the Prahran in 84. This somewhat tenuous connection with grapegrowing and winemaking was sufficient for them to acquire a long-term lease of the vineyard, and employ contract winemakers who have produced a series of wines since 08, collecting the trophy for Best Shiraz at the Victorian Wines Show 09, one silver and three bronze medals at the same show.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>