<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146021377</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/canberra-district/shepherds-run]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/canberra-district/shepherds-run]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Shepherds Run</name><region>Canberra District</region><address1>
            344 Norton Road, Wamboin, NSW 2620</address1><address2>
            
            Canberra District
            
            
        </address2><website>www.shepherdsrun.com.au</website><telephone>
            (02) 6238 3842
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Elke Davies, Canberra Winemakers
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            This is the venture of father Peter, wife Chris and daughter Elke Davies. In 1983 the family purchased what they describe as a clapped out sheep paddock on the side of a small valley with 180-degree views, 20 mins drive from Canberra. It was a gradual process, with Peter employed by the Federal Department of the Environment, and a background in agriculture dating back to the late 1960s. Elke became involved in hospitality as a part-time job while obtaining her first university degree; she then got a real job in the public service, and also lived in London for a while. Peter and Chris had given her 24 bottles of wine from her birth year for her 21st birthday, and all the pieces ultimately came together with her decision to enrol in the CSU wine science course. This in turn provoked the planting of a 2.5ha vineyard to equal amounts of merlot, riesling and pinot noir, and the opening of a caf/restaurant. Elke not only is trainee winemaker, but also chef and creator of the jams, sauces and chocolates available at the restaurant.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>