<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146042932</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/yarra-yarra]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/yarra-yarra]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Yarra Yarra</name><region>Yarra Valley</region><address1>
            239 Hunts Lane, Steels Creek, Vic 3775</address1><address2>
            
            Yarra Valley
            VIC
            
        </address2><website>www.yarrayarravineyard.com.au</website><telephone>
            (03) 5965 2380
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Ian Maclean
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (03) 5965 2086
        </facsimilie><description>
            Despite its small production, the wines of Yarra Yarra have found their way into a veritable whos who of Melbournes best restaurants, encouraging Ian Maclean to increase the estate plantings from 2ha to over 7ha in 1996 and 97. Demand for the beautifully crafted wines continued to exceed supply, so the Macleans planted yet more vines and increased winery capacity. All this seemed to go up in flames as the terrible 2009 Black Saturday bushfires consumed the winery, irreplaceable museum stock from 83 to 2000, the then yet-to-be-bottled 08 Syrah and 06 and 08 Sauvignon Blanc Semillon (the 07 vintage had been destroyed by frost), and scorched or burnt 50% of the estate vineyards. Friends rallied to the cause, and Ian has embarked on the long job of repairing/replacing the vineyard trellis system, methodically replanting the half of the vineyard destroyed by fire and introducing the use of organic/biodynamic sprays. The new winery was finished at the end of April 10, too late for the vintage, which was made in one of the farm buildings not destroyed. When friends asked why he should do all this, having turned 65, his answer was simple: My greatest wines have yet to be made. June 12 saw wines from the 11 vintage made in the new winery. Exports to Singapore, Malaysia, Taiwan and Hong Kong.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>