<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145982342</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/jaja]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/jaja]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>JaJa</name><region>Barossa Valley</region><address1>
            PO Box 3015, Strathmore, Vic 3041</address1><address2>
            
            Barossa Valley
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.jaja.com.au</website><telephone>
            0411 106 652
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Troy Kalleske (Contract)
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Brothers Bert and Pierre Werden are the faces behind www.winestar.com.au, which they describe as Australias leading online fine wine retailer. While it seemed a natural progression for them to develop JaJa as a family label, they say, Being in retail was a huge advantage in learning what not to do.On the positive side was the decision to concentrate on Barossa shiraz, the Stonewell subdistrict, 50-year-old vines, and the services of Troy Kalleske as winemaker. The Starlite wines are region-specific, small-batch wines that are sold to on-premise and fine wine off-premise businesses. Bert and Pierre say,The further we delved into the resources of our partner wineries, the more it became abundantly clear that the recent economic hardship had slowed the ability of even the biggest names to find a home either domestically or internationally for their premium fruit. The result was a vintage Mornington Peninsula bubbly, a single vineyard, high altitude Adelaide Hills chardonnay, and a Barossa shiraz, with more than a smidgeon of old vine material.  Exports to Singapore and Hong Kong.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>