<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146028058</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/central-victoria-zone/tar--rosestrust]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/central-victoria-zone/tar--rosestrust]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Tar &amp; Roses/Trust</name><region>Central Victoria Zone</region><address1>
            61 Vickers Lane, Nagambie, Vic 3608 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Central Victoria Zone
            VIC
            
        </address2><website>www.tarandroses.com.au</website><telephone>
            (03) 5794 1811
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Don Lewis, Narelle King
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            5 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (03) 5794 1833
        </facsimilie><description>
            Tar &amp; Roses is one of the more interesting new arrivals on the Australian winemaking scene, even though the partners, Don Lewis and Narelle King, have been making wine together for many years at Mitchelton and  for the past three years  Priorat, Spain. Don came from a grapegrowing family in Red Cliffs, near Mildura, and in his youth was press-ganged into working in the vineyard. When he left home he swore never to be involved in vineyards again, but in 1973 found himself accepting the position of assistant winemaker to Colin Preece at Mitchelton, where he remained until his retirement 32 years later. Narelle, having qualified as a chartered accountant, set off to travel, and while in South America met a young Australian winemaker who had just completed vintage in Argentina, and who lived in France. The lifestyle appealed greatly, so on her return to Australia she obtained her winemaking degree from CSU and was offered work by Mitchelton as a bookkeeper and cellar hand. Together they are making wines that are a mosaic of Australia, Italy and Spain in their inspiration.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>