<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145972089</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/margaret-river/gherardi]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/margaret-river/gherardi]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Gherardi</name><region>Margaret River</region><address1>
            PO Box 53, Margaret River, WA 6285</address1><address2>
            
            Margaret River
            WA
            
        </address2><website>www.gherardi.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 9757 3142
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Jurg Muggli, Simon Keall
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 9757 3180
        </facsimilie><description>
            Peter Gherardi is one of the most experienced viticulturists in WA, but has the habit of disappearing from time to time as he follows new paths. In 1979 he began the establishment of Freycinet Estate, while employed by the WA Dept of Agriculture as a viticulturist and oenologist (he already had a degree in Applied Science [Wine] at what is now known as Charles Sturt University). In 1991 he sold the winery and vineyard to Michael Wright; the much expanded operation is now Voyager Estate. Peter then became a viticultural consultant, but found time to work vintages in Bordeaux, Tuscany, Piedmont and Provence. Returning permanently to Australia, he became chief viticulturist at Xanadu Wines from 2001-05, also lecturing viticulture and oenology students at the Curtin University Margaret River campus. He bristles at the suggestion that his most recent venture is a hobby, even if it consumes weekends, weekdays given to his continuing role as a viticultural consultant. The ladybirds on the labels are a sign of a near chemical-free environment that has achieved a natural balance.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>