<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146013489</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/mclaren-vale/redheads-studios]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/mclaren-vale/redheads-studios]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Redheads Studios</name><region>McLaren Vale</region><address1>
            Cnr Foggo Road/Kangarilla Road, McLaren Vale, SA 5171</address1><address2>
            
            McLaren Vale
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.redheadswine.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 8323 7799
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Adam Hooper, Peter Kennedy
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 8323 0080
        </facsimilie><description>
            The Redheads Studio winery has always been, and will continue to be, constantly evolving, and a sometimes secret wine business, venture of young or youngish winemakers. It has its roots in the Flying Winemaker days of the late 1980s and 90s, when Australias best and brightest would travel to Europe for the northern hemisphere vintage, only to return home to continue their employment with mega wineries, unable to apply any of the ideas they picked up in Europe. Eventually, some money was scraped up to buy a former curry house restaurant called Redheads, and the founders saw no reason to change the name. It is now a place where small producers can come and go making their own wines behind closed doors in the dead of night, returning to work the following morning to their unsuspecting employer somewhat the worse for wear. It was inevitable that Redheads would start developing its own labels, and this it has done, the names of the wines giving further curry flavour to the venture. Exports to the UK, the US, Canada, Denmark and Singapore.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>