<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145950683</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/bobar]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/bobar]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Bobar</name><region>Yarra Valley</region><address1>
            253 Gulf Road, Yarra Glen, Vic 3775</address1><address2>
            
            Yarra Valley
            
            
        </address2><website/><telephone>
            (03) 9730 2668
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Tom and Sally Belford
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Tom and Sally Belford have worked full-time for vineyards and wineries in the cooler hilly parts of NSW, Macedon Ranges and Heathcote, but mostly and more recently in the Yarra Valley, where Tom is a winemaker at Sticks. Along the way they also managed to spend 15 months in France (with their two children), dividing their time between Champagne, Beaujolais, Provence, Cahors and Sauternes. In 2010 they decided to make a little wine for the hell of it, and purchased shiraz from the Yarraland Vineyard at Chirnside Park, run by the DAloisio family. It comes as close to natural wine as is possible, with whole bunches in an open fermenter, no crushing or destemming , no pigeage or pumping over, and no yeast. After eight days of carbonic maceration it was pressed to tank where it completed its alcoholic and malolactic fermentations, and remained on lees for four months before it was racked for the first and last time, and bottled without fining or filtration; prior to bottling a small sulphur dioxide addition of 20 ppm was made. It is sold by mail list via tomeb@iprimus.com.au and in a few bottle shops and restaurants in the Yarra Valley and Melbourne.  Exports to the UK.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>