<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145943505</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/heathcote/armstead-estate]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/heathcote/armstead-estate]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Armstead Estate</name><region>Heathcote</region><address1>
            366 Moorabbee Road, Knowsley, Vic 3523</address1><address2>
            
            Heathcote
            
            
        </address2><website>www.armsteadestate.com.au</website><telephone>
            (03) 5439 1363
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Peter Armstead
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Peter Armstead had been a lifelong wine collector and consumer when he was caught up in the Ansett collapse; he had been an aircraft engineer and technical instructor. While he and partner Sharon Egan have full-time day jobs, they were able to purchase a property on the shores of Lake Eppalock, beautiful even when the lake was empty. Now it is full, and they have a very attractive cellar door. They were determined to have a small vineyard, and proceeded to sequentially plant shiraz, marsanne and cabernet sauvignon, deliberately keeping the size of the plantings manageable. Within months of arriving in 2003, the first planting stage had been completed, Peter had joined the Heathcote Winegrowers Association and, before he knew it, had become secretary. He has used all of his numerous local contacts to learn as much as possible about viticulture and winemaking, and has also been able to buy grapes from well-known vineyards in the region. At first he was an observer and cellar assistant, but in 2009 he took the plunge and took over winemaking, but, he says, still with a little help from my friends.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>