<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145992981</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/canberra-district/maipenrai-vineyard--winery]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/canberra-district/maipenrai-vineyard--winery]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Maipenrai Vineyard &amp; Winery</name><region>Canberra District</region><address1>
            1516 Sutton Road, Sutton, NSW 2620 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Canberra District
            ACT
            
        </address2><website>www.maipenrai.com.au</website><telephone>
            (02) 8588 1217
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Brian Schmidt
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (02) 8588 1217
        </facsimilie><description>
            What a story this is, far too rich for just a few lines. It begins at Harvard, in 199293, where American-born Brian Schmidt and (now) wife (Australian) Jennifer Gordon were both working on their PhDs. Brian is presently a Laureate Fellow at the Australian National Universitys Mount Stromlo Observatory and in 2011 won the Nobel Prize for Astronomy. Prior to emigrating to Canberra in 95, he had formed a research team of 20 astronomers on five continents who used distant exploding stars to trace the expansion of the universe back in time; between then and now he has been awarded a constellation of awards and fellowships, undeterred by the tragic destruction of Mount Stromlo in the Canberra bushfires in 2003. In 1999 he and Jennifer purchased a property with a beautiful sloped hillside, and planted six clones of pinot noir; he was 33 at the time, and figured that by the time he was ready to retire, the vineyard would be well and truly into the prime of its life. An astronomers view indeed. In 2004 the first barrel of wine was made, followed by three barrels in 05 and two barrels in 06; in 07 all the wine was declassified into the Amungula Creek label, also used for wine made from small amounts of pinot grapes purchased from time to time from local growers. A 0.1ha trial of ultra-close spaced shiraz and viognier is underway.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>