<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146020191</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/clare-valley/seraphs-crossing]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/clare-valley/seraphs-crossing]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Seraph's Crossing</name><region>Clare Valley</region><address1>
            PO Box 5753, Clare, SA 5453</address1><address2>
            
            Clare Valley
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.seraphscrossing.com.au</website><telephone>
            0412 132 549
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Harry Dickinson
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            5 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            In a moment of enlightened madness, Harry Dickinson gave up his career as a lawyer in a major London law firm to work in the wine business. He helped run the International Wine Challenge for three years, followed by stints with various wine retailers, and some PR work for the German Wine Information Service. He worked his first vintage in Australia at Hardys Tintara winery in 1997 with Stephen Pannell and Larry Cherubino; their work with open fermenters, basket presses and winemaking philosophy made a huge impression. Following a period as a wine retailer in North Adelaide, he returned to winery work in 1999, in various wineries in the Clare Valley. During this time he and wife Chan bought a 75ha property. They restored the 1880s house on the property, and the vineyards have been extended from the original 1ha to now comprise shiraz (2ha), grenache, mourvedre and zinfandel (1ha each). The shiraz is hand-picked, de-stemmed, fermented with wild yeast, and, at the end of fermentation, is pressed directly to barrel where it remains for 28 months (with no racking) prior to blending and bottling with no fining or filtration. Exports to the UK, the US and Ireland.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>