<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146033974</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/queensland/granite-belt/twisted-gum-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/queensland/granite-belt/twisted-gum-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Twisted Gum Wines</name><region>Granite Belt</region><address1>
            2271 Eukey Road, Ballandean, Qld 4382 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Granite Belt
            QLD
            
        </address2><website>www.twistedgum.com.au</website><telephone>
            (07) 4684 1282
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Jim Barnes, Andy Williams (Contract)
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Tim and Michelle Coelli bring diverse and interesting backgrounds to this venture. During his university days in the early 1980s Tim began reading weekly wine columns of a certain journalist and bought recommended red wines from Wynns and Peter Lehmann, liked the wines, and with wife Michelle bought dozen and dozen.... Tim became a research economist, and during periods of living and working in Europe, he and Michelle became well acquainted with the wines of France, Spain and Italy. She has a degree in agricultural science which, she says,has not been well utilised because four children came along (currently aged 5 to 16). When they found a beautiful 40ha bush property on a ridge near Ballandean (at an altitude of 900m) with a little over 3ha of vines already planted, they did not hesitate. The vineyard was in need of TLC, and this has been provided in various ways, including the spreading of mulch under the vines to retain moisture, suppress weeds and improve soil structure. There is no cellar door (sales are through the website), and there is weekend accommodation in the newly renovated Twisted Gum Vineyard Cottage.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>