<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146030904</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/thick-as-thieves-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/thick-as-thieves-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Thick as Thieves Wines</name><region>Yarra Valley</region><address1>
            1 Symons Street, Healesville, Vic 3777 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Yarra Valley
            VIC
            
        </address2><website>www.tatwines.com.au</website><telephone>
            0417 184 690
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Syd Bradford
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Syd Bradford is living proof that small can be beautiful, and, equally, that an old dog can learn new tricks. A growing interest in good food and wine might have come to nothing had it not been for Pfeiffer Wines giving him a vintage job in 03. In that year he enrolled in the wine science course at CSU, moving to the Yarra Valley in 05. He gained experience at Coldstream Hills (vintage cellar hand), Rochford (assistant winemaker), Domaine Chandon (cellar hand) and Giant Steps/Innocent Bystander (assistant winemaker). In 06 Syd achieved the Deans Award of Academic Excellence at CSU and in 07 was the sole recipient of the A&amp;G Engineering Scholarship. Aged 35, he was desperate to have a go at crafting his own babies, and in 09 came across a small parcel of arneis from the Hoddles Creek area, and Thick as Thieves was born. In 10 he purchased small parcels of arneis, chardonnay, pinot noir and nebbiolo, making his wine in a home-away-from-home. The techniques used to make his babies could only come from someone who has spent a long time observing and thinking about what he might do.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>