<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145992202</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/lunar-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/lunar-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Lunar Wines</name><region>Barossa Valley</region><address1>
            RSD 108 Seppeltsfield Road, Marananga, SA 5355 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Barossa Valley
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.lunarwines.com.au</website><telephone>
            0427 186 295
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Corey Chaplin
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Corey Chaplin had served 3.5 years as an apprentice chef, but at the last moment decided winemaking rather than cheffing was where he wanted to go. He got a foot in the door picking grapes for Rolf Binder, doing a little home winemaking on the side; this was sufficient for him to get a cellar hand job at Rockford Wines the following vintage, and he remained at Rockford for the next four years working in most areas of the business. After spending all day at Rockford he would ride his bike to Paul Lindners Langmeil Wines, working on the red wines until the early hours of the morning, gaining a reputation as a lunatic. In 2004 he took the last step, selling his house and putting all the money into starting Lunar, sourcing grapes from Marananga, Greenock, Dorrien, Ebenezer and Seppeltsfield. If this werent enough, he alternated hemispheres, working in Spain for the 2006 and 07 vintages. It has to be said the high-alcohol style works much better with shiraz than it does with cabernet sauvignon from the Barossa Valley.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>