<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146017717</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/heathcote/ruperts-ridge-estate-vineyard]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/heathcote/ruperts-ridge-estate-vineyard]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Rupert's Ridge Estate Vineyard</name><region>Heathcote</region><address1>
            843 Metcalfe-Redesdale Road, Redesdale, Vic 3444 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Heathcote
            VIC
            
        </address2><website>www.rupertsridge.com</website><telephone>
            (03) 5425 3297
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Cobaw Ridge (Alan Cooper)
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            4 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (03) 5425 3297
        </facsimilie><description>
            Christina (Chris) Gillies and husband John Williams were grandparents before they embarked on a search for what became Ruperts Ridge in 2003. Armed with the bravery of ignorance, a book on how to plant a vineyard, and Alan Cooper of Cobaw Ridge to give advice in moments of crisis, they began planting 2.5ha of shiraz and viognier. There was no such thing as delegation; they planted the vines themselves, and came to know each one by name. Bloodied but unbowed, the following year they planted another 2 ha, mainly shiraz but with 0.25ha each of vermentino and sagrantino. The first crop (6 tonnes) came in 06, and over the next two years they retained 1 tonne (producing 70 dozen) selling the remainder of the grapes. The intention was to double the production in 09, but the terrible bushfires are more likely than not to have put paid to that. Chris and John were overseas, but last ditch defence by family friends, Redesdale locals and local winemakers largely saved the vineyard (though not the crop), but the house burnt down. A bit of adversity is not going to deter Chris and John from turning the galvanised iron former pig shed (which did survive the fire) into a cellar door, and once the house is rebuilt, it will be business as usual. The name, incidentally, is that of their great dane mastiff who provides a 24-hour security service, and escaped the fire.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>