<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146003510</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-hills/ngeringa]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-hills/ngeringa]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Ngeringa</name><region>Adelaide Hills</region><address1>
            119 Williams Road, Mount Barker, SA 5251</address1><address2>
            
            Adelaide Hills
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.ngeringa.com</website><telephone>
            (08) 8398 2867
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Erinn Klein
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            5 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 8398 2867
        </facsimilie><description>
            Erinn and Janet Klein say,As fervent practitioners of biodynamic wine growing, we respect biodynamics as a sensitivity to the rhythms of nature, the health of the soil and the connection between plant, animal and cosmos. It is a pragmatic solution to farming without the use of chemicals and a necessary acknowledgement that the farm unit is part of a great whole. It is not an easy solution, and the Kleins have increased the immensity of the challenge by using ultra-close vine spacing of 1.5m  1m, necessitating a large amount of hand training of the vines plus a tiny crawler tractor. Lest it be thought they have stumbled onto biodynamic growing without understanding wine science, they teamed up while studying at Adelaide University in 2000 (Erinn  oenology, Janet  viticulture/wine marketing), and then spent time looking at the great viticultural regions of the Old World, with a particular emphasis on biodynamics. The thick straw-bale walls of the winery result in a constant temperature throughout the year. The JE label is used for the basic wines, Ngeringa only for the very best. Exports to the UK, the US, Canada, Austria, Sweden and Japan.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>