<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145965474</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/other/various/domaines--vineyards]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/other/various/domaines--vineyards]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Domaines &amp; Vineyards</name><region>Various</region><address1>
            PO Box 6096, Swanbourne, WA 6010</address1><address2>
            
            Various
            ACT
            
        </address2><website>www.dandv.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 9384 4211
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Robert Bowen
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 9324 2155
        </facsimilie><description>
            One of the best-known winemakers in WA is Rob Bowen, with over 35 years experience with several of WAs leading wineries, most recently Houghton. In 2009 he joined forces with a team of viticulturists led by David Rado and other agricultural experts, who collectively furnish the project with an extensive range of knowledge and expertise. The theme is to produce premium wines with a strong sense of place through a virtual winery exercise, all grapes to be hand-picked from the best available vineyards in the Margaret River and Pemberton regions of southern WA. A second range under the Robert Bowen label will follow the same strategy, except for pricing, which will be at an affordable level. So long as the grape surplus continues, it is highly likely all of the wines will provide excellent value for money. At the present time sauvignon blanc, chardonnay and pinot noir are sourced from Pemberton, sauvignon blanc, semillon, cabernet sauvignon and merlot from Margaret River. Exports to the UK, the US, China, Singapore and Hong Kong.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>