<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145943889</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/clare-valley/artwine]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/clare-valley/artwine]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>ArtWine</name><region>Clare Valley</region><address1>
            ArtWine House, Springfarm Road, Clare, SA 5453</address1><address2>
            
            Clare Valley
            
            
        </address2><website>www.artwine.com.au</website><telephone>
            0411 422 450
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Joanne Irvine
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            25 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            This may be a relative newcomer on the winemaking front, but it has substantial vineyards dating back to 1997. It is the venture of Glen Kelly, owner of Harrison Research, who previously had senior roles with the Commonwealth Bank. Wife Judy also had many years in senior marketing roles in Australia and New York before the establishment of ArtWine. It has two vineyards, one on Springfarm Road, Clare, the other on Sawmill Road, Sevenhill. The Springfarm Road vineyard has a most interesting portfolio of grapes, the largest planting being 3.64ha of tempranillo, followed by (in descending order of size) riesling, pinot gris, cabernet sauvignon, grenache, cabernet franc, fiano, viognier and graciano. A further 2ha of fiano and 1.75ha of graciano were planted in the spring of 2011, replacing part of the cabernet block and the contoured section of the riesling block. The remainder of the cabernet sauvignon and riesling (plus cabernet franc) will be replanted over the next few years, the varieties yet to be decided. This is definitely a lateral approach by any standards. A second cellar door opened in 2012 in the Adelaide Hills (Bird in Hand Road,Woodside). Exports to Singapore.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>