<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145983643</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/tasmania/northern-tasmania/josef-chromy-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/tasmania/northern-tasmania/josef-chromy-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Josef Chromy Wines</name><region>Northern Tasmania</region><address1>
            370 Relbia Road, Relbia, Tas 7258</address1><address2>
            
            Northern Tasmania
            TAS
            
        </address2><website>www.josefchromy.com.au</website><telephone>
            (03) 6335 8700
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Jeremy Dineen
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            60 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (03) 6335 8777
        </facsimilie><description>
            Joe Chromy just refuses to lie down and admit that the wine industry in Tasmania is akin to a financial black hole. After escaping from Czechoslovakia in 1950, establishing Blue Ribbon Meats, using the proceeds of sale to buy Rochecombe and Heemskerk vineyards, then selling those and establishing Tamar Ridge before it, too, was sold, Joe is at it again; this time hes invested $40 million in a wine-based but multifaceted business, including a major building development in Launceston. If this were not remarkable enough, Joe is in his eighties, and has recovered from a major stroke. Foundation of the new wine business was the purchase of the large Old Stornoway Vineyard at a receivership sale in 2003; in all, there are 60ha of 10-year-old vines, the lions share to pinot noir and chardonnay. He retained Jeremy Dineen as winemaker, and the winery was completed prior to the 07 vintage. Chromys grandson Dean Cocker is business manager of the restaurant, function and wine centre, which has spectacular views over White Hills to Ben Lomond, the vineyard and the lakes. The homestead is now a dedicated wine centre and cellar door, offering WSET (Wine &amp; Spirit Education Trust) courses levels 1, 2 and 3. Exports to the UK, the US and other major markets have seen production increase significantly.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>