<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145951363</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/nagambie-lakes/box-grove-vineyard]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/nagambie-lakes/box-grove-vineyard]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Box Grove Vineyard</name><region>Nagambie Lakes</region><address1>
            PO Box 86, Avenel, Vic 3664</address1><address2>
            
            Nagambie Lakes
            
            
        </address2><website>www.boxgrovevineyard.com.au</website><telephone>
            (03) 5796 2626
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Sarah Gough
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            26 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            This is the venture of the Gough family, with industry veteran (and daughter) Sarah Gough managing the vineyard, winemaking and marketing. In 1995, having worked for Brown Brothers marketing department for 10 years, Sarah told Ross Brown she was leaving to get married and establish a family-owned farm near Tabilk. He immediately offered a 10-year contract to buy the grapes from 10ha each of shiraz and cabernet sauvignon; nervous about the long-term future, Sarah also planted 2.8ha of roussanne, promptly becoming the largest grower of the variety in the state. In 2007 Sarah decided to take a pre-emptive step of having five tonnes each of roussanne and shiraz roussanne made at Plunkett Fowles from the 08 vintage. Prior to the 09 vintage the supply agreement with Brown Brothers was not renewed (no surprise), leaving Sarah with a number of difficult decisions. The solution was to graft over 6ha of cabernet to 2ha of prosecco and 1ha each of viognier, vermentino, savagnin and primitivo, and manage Box Grove Vineyard as a fully fledged wine and verjus producer. Exports to China.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>