<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146037504</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-hills/warwick-billings]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-hills/warwick-billings]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Warwick Billings</name><region>Adelaide Hills</region><address1>
            C/- Post Office, Lenswood, SA 5240 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Adelaide Hills
            
            
        </address2><website>www.wowique.com.au</website><telephone>
            0405 437 864
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Warwick Billings
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            This is the venture of Warwick Billings and partner Rose Kemp. Warwick was a cider maker in the UK who came to study at Roseworthy, and got diverted into the wine world. He completed postgraduate oenology at Adelaide University in 1995, and worked for Miranda Wine, Orlando and Angove Family Winemakers from 2002 to 08, along the way moonlighting in France and Spain for 12 vintages. Warwicks approach to his eponymous label is self-deprecating, beginning with the name Wowique, and saying, Occasionally a vineyard sings to the winemaker. [We] have taken one of these songs and out it into a bottle. The vineyard in question is an unusual clone of chardonnay nurtured on a sloping hilltop site in Mt Torrens. The self-deprecation continues with the wine simply being labelled Wowique Blanc, which presumably sells because it is so good, not because of the name. Warwicks final word on all of this is, The winemaking is unashamedly inspired by Burgundy, but care is take to acknowledge that the soil is different, the clones are often different, the climate is definitely different, and the end consumer is usually different.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>