<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146010320</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/swan-district/pinelli-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/swan-district/pinelli-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Pinelli Wines</name><region>Swan District</region><address1>
            30 Bennett Street, Caversham, WA 6055</address1><address2>
            
            Swan District
            WA
            
        </address2><website>www.pinelliwines.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 9279 6818
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Robert and Daniel Pinelli
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 9377 4259
        </facsimilie><description>
            Domenic and Iolanda Pinelli emigrated from Italy in the mid-1950s, and it was not long before Domenic became employed by Waldeck Wines, then one of the Swan Valleys more important wineries. With the benefit of 20 years experience gained with Waldeck, in 1980 he purchased a 2.8ha vineyard that had been established many years previously. It became the site of the Pinelli family winery, cellar door and home vineyard, subsequently significantly expanded to its present level, with cabernet sauvignon, colombard, merlot and shiraz. Son Robert graduated with a degree in oenology from Roseworthy in 1987, and has been the winemaker at Pinelli for over 20 years. His brother Daniel obtained a degree in civil engineering from the University of WA in 94, but eventually the lure of the family winery became too strong, so he joined his brother in 02, and (using the distance education program) obtained his oenology degree from CSU in 07. He graduated with distinction, and was awarded the Domaine Chandon Sparkling Wine Award for best sparkling wine production student.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>