<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145944394</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/beechworth/a-rodda-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/beechworth/a-rodda-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>A. Rodda Wines</name><region>Beechworth</region><address1>
            PO Box 589, Beechworth, Vic 3747</address1><address2>
            
            Beechworth
            
            
        </address2><website/><telephone>
            0400 350 135
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Adrian Rodda
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Adrian Rodda has been winemaking since 1998, almost entirely working with David Bicknell at Oakridge. He was thus involved in the development of the superb Oakridge 864 Chardonnay, his final contribution to 864 coming in 2009. At the start of 2010 he and his wife Christie, a doctor, and their small but growing family, decided to move to Beechworth, and it was no coincidence that he was a long-term friend of viticulturist Mark Walpole. Yet further coincidences came with the Smith Vineyard and winery being available for lease; he now shares it with Mark Walpole, who makes his Beechworth wines there. Even more, was the availability of Smith Vineyard chardonnay, planted in 1974, and thus the release of the first A. Rodda wine. One should hardly be surprised that it is so good. Further down the track there will be a Yarra chardonnay from Murramong Vineyard, a single vineyard Tempranillo from Mark Walpoles vineyard in Beechworth, and a Bordeaux blend sourced predominantly from the old plantings on the Smith Vineyard.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>