<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145952537</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/eden-valley/brockenchack]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/eden-valley/brockenchack]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Brockenchack</name><region>Eden Valley</region><address1>
            13/102 Burnett Street, Buderim, Qld 4556 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Eden Valley
            
            
        </address2><website>www.brockenchack.com.au</website><telephone>
            (07) 5458 7710
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Shawn Kalleske
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            16 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Trevor (and wife Marilyn) Harch have long been involved in liquor distribution in Qld, owning one of Australias leading independent liquor wholesalers, servicing licensed premises throughout Qld. Over the years, he became a regular visitor to the Barossa/Eden Valley region, and in 1999 purchased the historic Tanunda Cellars Wine Store. This encouraged him to purchase a wine store at Maleny, renamed Purple Palate, and spawning four other Purple Palate retail bottle shops across Brisbane and the Sunshine Coast, plus the premier wine bar in Brisbane city, known as Bar Barossa. But that is only part of the story: in 2007,Trevor and Marilyn purchased a 16ha vineyard in the Eden Valley and retained friend Shawn Kalleske as winemaker. The vineyard has 8ha of shiraz, 2ha each of riesling and cabernet sauvignon, and 1.3ha each of pinot noir, pinot gris and chardonnay. The name of the business is appropriately Delphic. While every wine so far released, and those planned for the future, are labelled in honour of one or other of the Marchs family, Brockenchack comes from the Christian names of the four grandchildren: Bronte, Mackenzie, Charli and Jack.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>