<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146011220</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/orange/printhie-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/orange/printhie-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Printhie Wines</name><region>Orange</region><address1>
            489 Yuranigh Road, Molong, NSW 2866</address1><address2>
            
            Orange
            NSW
            
        </address2><website>www.printhiewines.com.au</website><telephone>
            (02) 6366 8422
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Drew Tuckwell
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (02) 6366 9328
        </facsimilie><description>
            Owned by the Swift family, Printhie has established itself at the forefront of quality viticulture and winemaking in Orange. The estate vineyards have matured and fruit intake is supplemented by contract growers, avoiding the fruit salad vineyard approach by sourcing fruit from the best growers in the best sites with the best varietal match. The new generation at Printhie continues to make its mark with Ed Swift, former President of the Orange Region Vignerons Association and a participant of the Future Leaders Program. Winemaker Drew Tuckwell is a Len Evans Tutorial scholar and participant in the Wine Communicators of Australia Young Guns and Gurus program (as a young gun). The wine portfolio has been consolidated: the entry-level Mountain Range now comprises just six wines (three white, three red), the Mount Canobolas Collection (MCC) range is a quasi-reserve range, and the Swift Family Heritage flagship range has been trimmed to just one red wine (a Cabernet Sauvignon/Shiraz blend). Exports to the US, Denmark, Ivory Coast and China.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>