<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145991504</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/long-gully-estate]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/victoria/yarra-valley/long-gully-estate]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Long Gully Estate</name><region>Yarra Valley</region><address1>
            Long Gully Road, Healesville, Vic 3777</address1><address2>
            
            Yarra Valley
            VIC
            
        </address2><website>www.longgullyestate.com</website><telephone>
            (03) 9510 5798
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Han Tao Lau
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            21 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (03) 9510 9859
        </facsimilie><description>
            Owned by Reiner and Irma Klapp, this is one of the larger Yarra Valley producers to have successfully established a number of export markets, doubtless due to its core of mature vineyards, which have grown from 2.2ha to over 20 ha, underlining its commercial success. There have been various winemaking changes over recent years, culminating with the appointment of Han Tao Lau as winemaker in Nov 10. Han came to Australia to study wine business at the University of Adelaide, intending to open a boutique wine store in his home city of Hong Kong. Instead, he fell in love with winemaking, and completed the graduate diploma in oenology. He has worked for wineries including the icon Chteau Valandraud in St Emilion and Weingut Okonomierat Rebholz in Pfalz, Germany; over the past six years he has been in the Yarra Valley, with vintages at Coldstream Hills, then Domaine Chandon, followed by two years as assistant winemaker at Yarra Yering. He has been joined by newly appointed viticulturist Aaron Bailey. Exports to the UK, Switzerland, Singapore and China.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>