<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145995957</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/margaret-river/merops-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/margaret-river/merops-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Merops Wines</name><region>Margaret River</region><address1>
            5992 Caves Road, Margaret River, WA 6825</address1><address2>
            
            Margaret River
            WA
            
        </address2><website>www.meropswines.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 9757 9195
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Flying Fish Cove (Elizabeth Reed), Jurg Muggli
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 9757 3193
        </facsimilie><description>
            Jim and Yvonne Ross have been involved in horticulture for over 25 years, in production, retail nurseries and viticulture. They established a nursery and irrigation business in the Margaret River township in 1985 before establishing a rootstock nursery. In 2000 they removed the nursery and planted cabernet sauvignon, cabernet franc, merlot and shiraz on the laterite gravel over clay soils. They use the practices developed by Professor William Albrecht in the US 50 years ago, providing mineral balance and thus eliminating the need for insecticides and toxic sprays. Organic pre-certification was completed in 2007, which resulted in the 08 vintage being certified organic. Over the years the wines have won numerous bronze medals at Australian wine shows, Ornatus having particular success at the International Wine &amp; Spirit Competition (London), with Best in Class silver medals. No wines were received for this edition, the rating is that of last year.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>