<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146013983</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/clare-valley/rhythm-stick]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/clare-valley/rhythm-stick]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Rhythm Stick Wines</name><region>Clare Valley</region><address1>
            PO Box 270, Clare, SA 5453</address1><address2>
            
            Clare Valley
            
            
        </address2><website>www.rhythmstickwines.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 8843 4325
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Tim Adams
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Rhythm Stick has come a long way in a short time, and with a small vineyard. It is owned by Ron and Jeanette Ely, who in 1997 purchased a 3.2ha property at Penwortham. The couple had already decided that in the future they would plant a vineyard, and simply to obtain experience they planted 135 cabernet sauvignon cuttings from Waninga Vineyards in four short rows. Since 2006 they have produced 26 dozen bottles of Cabernet a year, making the wine and sharing it with friends. In 02 they planted riesling, and the first harvest followed in 06, the grapes from this and the ensuing two vintages sold to Clare Valley winemakers. Prior to the 09 harvest they were advised that due to the GFC no grapes would be required, which simply operated to advance Ron's planned retirement after 40 years in electrical engineering consulting and management. The 09 vintage produced 20 tonnes of fruit, and the wines had what can only be described as spectacular success for a first-time producer. The high yield for a young, dry-grown vineyard comes about because of the ideal combination of rich, red-brown loam over sandstone reef structures with limestone and slate components, including areas of perched water. This has resulted in full canopy cover in drought conditions.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>