<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145946147</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/other/various/barokes-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/other/various/barokes-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Barokes Wines</name><region>Various</region><address1>
            111 Cecil Street, South Melbourne, Vic 3205 (postal)</address1><address2>
            
            Various
            ACT
            
        </address2><website>www.wineinacan.com</website><telephone>
            (03) 9675 4349
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Steve Barics
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (03) 9675 4594
        </facsimilie><description>
            Barokes packages its wines in aluminium cans. The filling process is patented, and the wine has been in commercial production since 2003. The wines show normal maturation and none of the cans used since start-up shows signs of corrosion. Wines are supplied in bulk by large wineries in South Eastern Australia, with Peter Scudamore-Smith acting as blending consultant. Year after year, my tastings give rise to tasting notes with no mention of reduction or any other fault. The technology has now been licensed by global packaging company Ball Packaging Europe, which will see more producers selling wines in cans in Europe; in Australia Barokes is offering customised canning for Australian companies. Barokes has now won a series of awards, with gold medals and a trophy in wine competitions in California and Europe. The day Barokes wins a gold medal, let alone a trophy, in an Australian wine show, I will be the first to congratulate it. Exports to all major markets with increasing success, with production rising to 300 000 cases (24 cans per case). Exports to all major markets with increasing success, with production rising to 300 000 cases (24 cans per case).
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>