<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145944393</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/southern-new-south-wales-zone/a-retief]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/new-south-wales/southern-new-south-wales-zone/a-retief]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>A. Retief</name><region>Southern New South Wales Zone</region><address1>
            PO Box 2503, Strawberry Hills, NSW 2012</address1><address2>
            
            Southern New South Wales Zone
            NSW
            2012
        </address2><website>www.aretief.com.au</website><telephone>
            0400 650 530
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Alex Retief
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (02) 8569 2048
        </facsimilie><description>
            Owner and winemaker Alex Retiefs wine career was prompted by his parents planting a vineyard near Ladysmith, in the Gundagai region, in 1997. The following year he enrolled in the wine science course at CSU, and in 2001 was accepted as the trainee winemaker at the universitys winery under Greg Gallagher. In mid 02 he went to Californias Sonoma Valley for four months, working at Fetzer Vineyards, returning to the Hunter Valley for the 03 vintage with Andrew Margan. He was winemaker there for two and a half years, punctuated by a harvest in Languedoc in 04, before heading back to France in 05 for a two-year appointment as winemaker at Chateau de Lagarde in Bordeaux. Since then he has worked for Peter Lehmann Wines in Sydney as a sales representative, thereafter starting his own boutique wine distribution company. Its portfolio includes A. Retief, imported wines from Chateau de Lagarde, and local wines Eden Road, Cape Bernier, Capanno and Lawsons. The A. Retief wines are made from contract-grown grapes in the Tumbarumba/Canberra District/Hilltops/Gundagai regions.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>