<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145982343</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/jamabro-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/barossa-valley/jamabro-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Jamabro Wines</name><region>Barossa Valley</region><address1>
            PO Box 434, Tanunda, SA 5352</address1><address2>
            
            Barossa Valley
            SA
            
        </address2><website>www.jamabro.com.au</website><telephone>
            0437 633 575
        </telephone><winemaker>
            David Heinze
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 8563 3837
        </facsimilie><description>
            Sixth-generation grapegrower David Heinze and wife Juli moved into winemaking in 2003, just as many of the major companies reduced their intake of Barossa grapes. With a little over 20ha of vines planted to eight varieties, they started with a full suite of wines, using estate-grown grapes and carrying out all the winemaking (other than bottling) onsite. Real marketing skill is involved with the labelling (Jamabro is taken from a combination of family names). The Semillon takes the name of daughter Madison who, having just had her hair straightened for a school photograph, was doused in semillon when a bung came out unexpectedly, causing lengthy and messy re-straightening (and an aversion to the winery); and Mums Spade Shiraz celebrates the spade given to Davids mum when she turned 21. Wherever Mum went, so did her spade... When there was something to dig, out of the car boot came the spade. We lost Mum in 2006. Mums Spade Shiraz is our tribute to Mum and all the other great Australian farming women, often the quiet achievers. Exports to Singapore.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>