<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145956596</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-zone/caught-redhanded]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/south-australia/adelaide-zone/caught-redhanded]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Caught Redhanded</name><region>Adelaide Zone</region><address1>
            1 Esplanade, Sellicks Beach, SA 5174</address1><address2>
            
            Adelaide Zone
            SA
            
        </address2><website/><telephone>
            0419 252 967
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Phil Rogers, Linda Domas (Consultant)
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            Phil Rogers, a casualty of the 2001 Ansett Airlines collapse, enrolled at the start of 02 in the CSU Bachelor of Wine Science program, completing his first vintage in 03 at Rosemount in McLaren Vale. His practical training involved 12 months as the trainee winemaker under the direction of Adrian Drumm at the Charles Sturt winery, followed by vintage at Hardys Chateau Reynella, later in the same year making Brunello de Montalcino and Chianti Classico in Tuscany, then back to commercial production in 07 with McLaren Vale Shiraz and Adelaide Hills Syrah. Aromatic whites followed in 08, and in 09 the portfolio was expanded to include very small quantities of Adelaide Hills Pinot Noir, Pinot Gris and Merlot, Langhorne Creek Cabernet Sauvignon and continuing Shiraz. This hectic pace was easy meat for someone who had spent the last four years of his career with Ansett in the high-stress world of airline operations, dealing with bad weather, broken aircraft, sick flight attendants and unpaid pilots.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>