<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>145970594</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/other/various/fletcher-wines]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/other/various/fletcher-wines]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Fletcher Wines</name><region>Various</region><address1>
            90 Gold Street, Collingwood, Vic 3066</address1><address2>
            
            Various
            
            
        </address2><website>www.fletcherwines.com</website><telephone>
            0403 302 729
        </telephone><winemaker>
            David Fletcher
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            Not Available
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            Not Available
        </facsimilie><description>
            David Fletcher has a background that would make any Florentine Renaissance man proud. While completing his oenology course at Adelaide University, he worked filling flagons and tending vines at Tinlins in McLaren Vale. On graduation in 2003, he worked for OLeary Walker in the Clare Valley for two years; for reasons not entirely self-evident, this inspired him to work in Burgundy, and in 04 he worked harvest at Domaine Chevrot. In love with pinot, he moved to the Yarra Valley at the start of 06, where he stayed for three years as assistant winemaker at Sticks, while fitting in a northern hemisphere vintage each year, once in Kazakhstan, and twice in Italy for Ceretto. In 2009, he became a grape liaison officer with Fosters, with responsibilities extending across Vic and parts of NSW, the object being the assessment of grape quality and determining picking dates. This job then offered him the opportunity to fill the same role in the Napa Valley and Santa Barbara County for Beringer, part of Fosters.Agatha Christie would quickly find the link that led David and wife Eleanor to establish Fletcher Wines, dedicated solely to making Nebbiolo from vines at least 10 years old.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>