<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><extraction><clueid>146038302</clueid><fullpath><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/geographe/whicher-ridge]]></fullpath><theme>WinerySearchDetailsNick1</theme><middle>default</middle><baseURI><bucketBaseURI><bucketName>WineryInfoDetails</bucketName><uri><![CDATA[http://www.winecompanion.com.au/wineries/western-australia/geographe/whicher-ridge]]></uri></bucketBaseURI></baseURI>
<WineryInfoDetails><item><name>Whicher Ridge</name><region>Geographe</region><address1>
            182 Chapman Hill East Road, Busselton, WA 6280</address1><address2>
            PO Box 1060 Busselton </address2><website>www.whicherridge.com.au</website><telephone>
            (08) 9753 1394
        </telephone><winemaker>
            Cathy Howard
        </winemaker><wineryards>
            5 hectares
        </wineryards><facsimilie>
            (08) 9753 1394
        </facsimilie><description>
            It is hard to imagine a founding husband-and-wife team with such an ideal blend of viticultural and winemaking experience accumulated over a collective 40-plus years. Cathy Howard (ne Spratt) was a winemaker for 16 years at Orlando and St Hallett in the Barossa Valley, and at Watershed Wines in Margaret River. She now has her own winemaking consulting business covering the southwest regions of WA, as well as making the Whicher Ridge wines. Neil Howards career as a viticulturist spans more than 25 years, beginning in the Pyrenees region with Taltarni Vineyards and Blue Pyrenees Estate, before moving to Mount Avoca as vineyard manager for 12 years. When he moved to the west, he managed the Sandalford Wines vineyard in Margaret River for several years, then developed and managed a number of smaller vineyards throughout the region. Whicher Ridges Odyssey Creek Vineyard at Chapman Hill has 2.5ha of sauvignon blanc, 1.8ha of cabernet sauvignon and 0.7ha of viognier. The Howards have chosen the Frankland River subregion of the Great Southern to supply shiraz and riesling, and also intend to buy grapes from Margaret River.
        </description></item></WineryInfoDetails></extraction>